Ng Kwong Cheong Tokyo-to, Katsushika-ku, Higashi Kanamachi 1-36-2, 4th building room number 225, 125-0041 080-31713321 setsunafseiei_nkc@hotmail.com nkc900201@gmail.com



SUMMARY

A software developer who aspires to be a full stack developer that can apply the concepts of AI technology in working practices with almost 4 years of software development experience working on various industries. At the same time, I'm also a master graduate student in the study of deep learning specializing in computer vision and image processing. Currently working as a PHP developer but also a machine learning enthusiast who self-learned Python programming and AI-related case studies.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Languages

- Proficiency in: PHP, Python
- Intermediate in: HTML, Javascript, CSS
- Familiar with: Java (2+ years of experience while working in Malaysia)

Framework

- Frontend: Vue
- UI rendering: Buefy, Bulma
- Server-side rendering: InertiaJS
- Backend: Laravel (PHP), Struts (Java)
- Database: MySQL, MS SQL
- Source code version control: Git

Development Tools

- Database: dBeaver, Microsoft SQL Server
- Source version control: Github, Gitlab, Sourcetree
- Operating System: Microsoft Windows 10, Linux Ubuntu 20.0 (WSL)
- IDE: Eclipse IDE (Java), Microsoft Visual Studio, Microsoft VS Code, Anaconda IDE, Pycharm

EXPERIENCE

System Engineer

Dec 2020 - Current

株式会社ドコマップジャパン (Minato-ku, Tokyo)

- Full-stack development of company's product in web application development using PHP Laravel framework
- Review, analysis and modifications of product's system using software development cycle process methodology
- Time-to-time monitoring and maintenance of company's application system based on task ticketing using Gitlab source code management

Software Engineer Oct 2016 – Aug 2018

Software International Corporation Sdn Bhd (Malaysia)

Support and maintenance of client's daily operation system using Java EE Struts framework

- · Review, analysis and modifications of Java-based application system
- Time-to-time monitoring of company's application system

Software Engineer

Jul 2015 - Sep 2016

Syscatech Sdn Bhd (Malaysia)

- · Web-based application development and support of electronic multi-level marketing system
- Research in implementing scalable Java-based application system using Java EE Hibernate framework
- Review, analysis and medication of company's products

Graduate Trainee Jul 2014 – June 2015

Advanced Micro Devices Global Services (M)

- Perform monthly routine tasks on a rotation basis based on team assignment
- Generate daily reports on daily working progress
- · Problem-solved assigned tasks using Microsoft Visual Studio with C#, and Eclipse IDE with Java

LANGUAGES

English

- Bilingual proficiency
- TOEFL IBT (2020) 101/120

Mandarin

Native Speaker

English

Native speaker

Malay

Bilingual proficiency

Japanese

- Intermediate Listener, Novice Speaker, Intermediate reading and writing
- JLPT N2 level

EDUCATION

Soka University

Sep 2018 - Sep 2020

Hachioji-shi, Tokyo Japan

· Master of Science in Engineering

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman

May 2010 - Aug 2014

Kampar, Perak Malaysia

 Bachelor of Information Technology (Hons) Computer Engineering, Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

HONORS AND AWARDS

Soka University

Sep 2018 - Sep 2020

Hachioji-shi, Tokyo Japan

- Makiguchi Scholarship recipient
- Schlieman Award

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman

May 2010 - Aug 2014

Kampar, Perak Malaysia

• Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

PUBLICATIONS

(Peer Reviewed)

- Ng, Kwong Cheong, Murata, Yuki and Masayasu, Atsumi, Traffic Risk Estimation from On-vehicle Video by Region-based Spatio-temporal DNN trained using Comparative Loss, Proceedings of the 33rd Annual Conference of the Japanese Society for Artificial Intelligence, June. 04-07, 2019
- Ng, Kwong Cheong, Murata, Yuki and Masayasu Atsumi, Performance Enhancement of Region-based Spatio-temporal Neural Network for Traffic Risk Estimation using Real and Virtual Datasets, Proceedings of the 34th Annual Conference of the Japanese Society for Artificial Intelligence, June. 09-11, 2020.

WEBSITE

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/kwongcheongng/
- https://nkc900201.wixsite.com/kclovinit